T 6238 6863

E samuelfong5005@gmail.com
L linkedin.com/in/samuelfongky

P samuelfongky.github.io/Profile

#### **SKILLS**

Data Analysis

Accounting Basics

Technical Analysis

**Project Scheduling** 

Collaboration

Interpersonal Skills

Organizing Skills

#### **SOFTWARE**

#### **Computer Programming**

(Python, C++, R, JavaScript, MATLAB, HTML, CSS, PHP, C, C#, Objective-c, Java, Bootstrap, DOM, jQuery, React, JSON, SQL, Swift, Kotlin)

#### Microsoft Office Suite

(VBA, Excel, Word, PowerPoin Visio, Power BI, Access)

#### **Dashboarding Tools**

(Tableau, Databox, Miro Lucidchart)

## Database Management

(MySQL, Docker, PhpMyAdmin, Xampp, AWS, Azure, Mongodb, Typeform, Postman, GitHub)

#### Discrete-Event Simulation Model

(Arena Anylogic)

#### Web Developing

(Node.is. ReactJS)

#### Mobile App Developing

(Xcode, Android Studio

Mobile App / Website Designing

#### Machine Learning Model

Cara MI Vala Tancarflaw

#### Multimedia Editing

(Photoshop, Illustrator, Canva, Premiere, Aftereffects, Audition, Procreate, Vegas, Powerdirector,

#### Social Media

(Facebook, Instagram, Twitter)

#### **LANGUAGES**

Fluency in Cantonese, Mandarin, English

# FONG KING YUI, SAMUEL

Energetic and passionate fresh graduate working towards a BEng in FinTech at the Chinese University of Hong Kong and MSc student in ISM at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, with wide variety of working experience specializing in Computer Science and Data Analysis. Equipped with great enthusiasm in both engineering and financial industry.

## **RELATED WORKING EXPERIENCE**

# **Emerging Technologies Solutions Consultant Intern**

2022/06 - Present, HKT Limited

# **Technical Project Assistant & Student Mentor**

2020/01 – 2022/06, Centre for Learning Sciences and Technologies, The Chinese University of Hong Kong

#### **Business Analyst Programmer Intern**

2021/07 - 2021/08, China Tonghai International Financial Limited

## Data Science, I&T Associate

2020/12 - 2021/01, Inclusive Business Lab

# Software Engineer (Web / IOS / Android) & Data Scientist Intern 2020/07 – 2020/09, MotoNerv Limited

#### **EDUCATION**

# MSc Student in Information Systems Management

2022/08 - Present, The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

## BEng in Financial Technology

(Double minors in **Computer Science** and **Data Analytics and Informatics**) 2018/09 – 2022/07, The Chinese University of Hong Kong

#### **OTHER WORKING EXPERIENCE**

#### **Administrative Assistant**

2019/10 – 2019/11, Centre for Innovation and Technology, The Chinese University of Hong Kong

## **Events Coordinator**

2019/07 – 2019/08, Information Technology Service Centre, The Chinese University of Hong Kong

## **Clerk & Class Tutor**

2018/10 - 2020/06, Valtorta College

#### Salesman

2018/06 – 2018/08, Broadway Photo Supply Limited 2017/05 – 2019/05, Christian Dior Hong Kong Limited

## **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES EXPERIENCE**

#### **Executive Committee**

2020/02 – 2021/02, System Engineering and Engineering Management Society, The Student Union of the Chinese University of Hong Kong 2020/02 – 2021/02, Shaw Band, the Chinese University of Hong Kong

#### Chairman

2016/10 - 2017/10, Student Union, Valtorta College

## **AWARDS**

# **Targeted Taught Postgraduate Programmes Fellowships**

University Grants Committee

# **Concord Fortune Ming Tak Scholarship**

Concord Fortune Charity Foundation

## Children Charity Foundation Charity Scholarship

Children Charity Foundation

#### **Woo Fung Miu Ling Scholarship**

Valtorta College

#### The TOYPA 2018 Future Leader

The Outstanding Young Persons' Association